{"topic_id": 3, "uuid": "01b7d059-893b-4152-a31b-6661b78e59c1", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'The congressional certification of Joe Biden’s victory was halted.'?", "option_A": "Protesters clashed with police and breached security barriers at the Capitol.", "option_B": "The information provided is insufficient to determine the cause.", "option_C": "A woman was shot inside the Capitol and died.", "option_D": "Pipe bombs were reported at the Republican National Committee building and the Democratic National Committee headquarters.", "golden_answer": "A"}
{"topic_id": 3, "uuid": "c0cd1b7a-dead-4c94-9459-ad96b031ef5c", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'Capitol Police Chief Steven Sund, House Sergeant at Arms Paul Irving, and Senate Sergeant at Arms Michael Stenger resigned.'?", "option_A": "The information provided is insufficient to determine the cause.", "option_B": "The FBI and ATF cleared the Capitol.", "option_C": "Trump urged supporters to march to the Capitol.", "option_D": "Pipe bombs were reported at the Republican National Committee building and the Democratic National Committee headquarters.", "golden_answer": "C"}
{"topic_id": 1, "uuid": "6d32b8c0-8028-4280-94af-cd3326ecfc78", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'The British pound plunged in value.'?", "option_A": "The information provided is insufficient to determine the cause.", "option_B": "The Conservative Party won the election.", "option_C": "The UK voted to leave the EU in a June 23 referendum.", "option_D": "Prime Minister David Cameron pledged a referendum on EU membership in 2013.", "golden_answer": "C,D"}
{"topic_id": 3, "uuid": "26317e24-331b-4efe-80aa-12f843efa98b", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'A woman was shot inside the Capitol and died.'?", "option_A": "Protesters clashed with police and breached security barriers at the Capitol.", "option_B": "The House and Senate recessed, and the Capitol was locked down.", "option_C": "Pipe bombs were reported at the Republican National Committee building and the Democratic National Committee headquarters.", "option_D": "Supporters stormed the U.S. Capitol.", "golden_answer": "A,B,D"}
{"topic_id": 3, "uuid": "65f13f7b-e818-48db-871c-ca4d93ef1d21", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'Congress confirmed Biden as president in the early hours of January 7th.'?", "option_A": "The FBI and ATF cleared the Capitol.", "option_B": "The House and Senate recessed, and the Capitol was locked down.", "option_C": "A woman was shot inside the Capitol and died.", "option_D": "The Capitol was secured, and lawmakers reconvened to continue certification.", "golden_answer": "A,B,D"}
{"topic_id": 3, "uuid": "296a8f9d-dfcb-4439-861e-69a96fb655f8", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'The D.C. National Guard was activated, and a citywide curfew was imposed.'?", "option_A": "Protesters clashed with police and breached security barriers at the Capitol.", "option_B": "Trump supporters protested in Washington, D.C.", "option_C": "The information provided is insufficient to determine the cause.", "option_D": "A woman was shot inside the Capitol and died.", "golden_answer": "A,B"}
{"topic_id": 3, "uuid": "69697d8d-eba2-4534-ae6f-ee6f47ed1039", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'Capitol Police Chief Steven Sund, House Sergeant at Arms Paul Irving, and Senate Sergeant at Arms Michael Stenger resigned.'?", "option_A": "Pipe bombs were reported at the Republican National Committee building and the Democratic National Committee headquarters.", "option_B": "The congressional certification of Joe Biden’s victory was halted.", "option_C": "Trump addressed the crowd.", "option_D": "Trump supporters protested in Washington, D.C.", "golden_answer": "B,C,D"}
{"topic_id": 1, "uuid": "3bd1737f-e862-4bbd-a51e-bede723cbf78", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'Nicola Sturgeon stated the Scottish government would prepare legislation for a new independence referendum.'?", "option_A": "David Cameron announced his resignation as Prime Minister.", "option_B": "Global markets plunged following the Brexit vote.", "option_C": "The nation divided into 'remain' and 'leave' camps.", "option_D": "The United Kingdom held a referendum on June 23.", "golden_answer": "B,C,D"}
{"topic_id": 3, "uuid": "f82c0445-6681-4f27-a1da-951b95bc07ce", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'The FBI and ATF cleared the Capitol.'?", "option_A": "Trump supporters protested in Washington, D.C.", "option_B": "The House and Senate recessed, and the Capitol was locked down.", "option_C": "The information provided is insufficient to determine the cause.", "option_D": "Protesters clashed with police and breached security barriers at the Capitol.", "golden_answer": "A,B,D"}
{"topic_id": 3, "uuid": "c396a381-fdc2-4a30-a168-beb1fd90d800", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'The FBI and ATF cleared the Capitol.'?", "option_A": "Protesters clashed with police and breached security barriers at the Capitol.", "option_B": "Pipe bombs were reported at the Republican National Committee building and the Democratic National Committee headquarters.", "option_C": "The House and Senate recessed, and the Capitol was locked down.", "option_D": "Five people died during the riots.", "golden_answer": "A,C"}
{"topic_id": 3, "uuid": "33da63e6-035c-4134-b1d8-da5c27722c2f", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'A woman was shot inside the Capitol and died.'?", "option_A": "The information provided is insufficient to determine the cause.", "option_B": "The House and Senate recessed, and the Capitol was locked down.", "option_C": "Trump supporters protested in Washington, D.C.", "option_D": "Pipe bombs were reported at the Republican National Committee building and the Democratic National Committee headquarters.", "golden_answer": "B,C"}
{"topic_id": 3, "uuid": "04e7ebbc-7638-42f1-9df8-10f856fd6b51", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'Trump was impeached for a second time on January 13th.'?", "option_A": "Protesters clashed with police and breached security barriers at the Capitol.", "option_B": "Twitter removed Trump's tweets and locked his account.", "option_C": "Congress confirmed Biden as president in the early hours of January 7th.", "option_D": "The Capitol was secured, and lawmakers reconvened to continue certification.", "golden_answer": "A"}
{"topic_id": 4, "uuid": "cb335bff-b0e7-4a66-94bc-ed3f49500372", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'Shinzo Abe visited Jerusalem in 2018.'?", "option_A": "Shinzo Abe offered to host a peace summit in 2017.", "option_B": "Benjamin Netanyahu visited Tokyo in 2014.", "option_C": "Shinzo Abe returned to office in 2012 and later became the longest-serving prime minister.", "option_D": "Shinzo Abe reinterpreted Japan's constitution in 2014.", "golden_answer": "A"}
{"topic_id": 4, "uuid": "9d7a89c2-3706-41b5-b459-0b5b1ec88053", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'Videos of the assassination circulated on social media.'?", "option_A": "Shinzo Abe promoted the Quadrilateral Security Dialogue (Quad).", "option_B": "Shinzo Abe coined the phrase 'a free and open Indo-Pacific'.", "option_C": "Former Japanese Prime Minister Shinzo Abe was assassinated at a campaign rally.", "option_D": "Explosives were found at Tetsuya Yamagami's home.", "golden_answer": "C"}
{"topic_id": 3, "uuid": "f178508b-ff4d-4651-8ae4-428694475a59", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'Twitter removed Trump's tweets and locked his account.'?", "option_A": "Protesters clashed with police and breached security barriers at the Capitol.", "option_B": "Congress confirmed Biden as president in the early hours of January 7th.", "option_C": "Pipe bombs were reported at the Republican National Committee building and the Democratic National Committee headquarters.", "option_D": "The congressional certification of Joe Biden’s victory was halted.", "golden_answer": "A,B,D"}
{"topic_id": 1, "uuid": "cf1f8837-027b-433d-a37f-86c1f9925c83", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'The British pound plunged in value.'?", "option_A": "David Cameron announced his resignation as Prime Minister.", "option_B": "The Conservative Party won the election.", "option_C": "The information provided is insufficient to determine the cause.", "option_D": "The United Kingdom held a referendum on June 23.", "golden_answer": "D"}
{"topic_id": 4, "uuid": "320ade07-c1bf-45a8-9634-a8fee8103d2b", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'Shinzo Abe reinterpreted Japan's constitution in 2014.'?", "option_A": "Shinzo Abe became the deputy chief cabinet secretary in the early 2000s.", "option_B": "The information provided is insufficient to determine the cause.", "option_C": "Shinzo Abe became the youngest prime minister in postwar Japan in 2006.", "option_D": "Shinzo Abe returned to office in 2012 and later became the longest-serving prime minister.", "golden_answer": "D"}
{"topic_id": 3, "uuid": "039f3ecb-76ac-4a92-a447-599e4d6805b9", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'Supporters stormed the U.S. Capitol.'?", "option_A": "Pipe bombs were reported at the Republican National Committee building and the Democratic National Committee headquarters.", "option_B": "The information provided is insufficient to determine the cause.", "option_C": "Protesters clashed with police and breached security barriers at the Capitol.", "option_D": "Trump supporters protested in Washington, D.C.", "golden_answer": "C,D"}
{"topic_id": 3, "uuid": "510e017c-2cdc-4c03-b2b9-be6b0125cd4f", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'Trump was impeached for a second time on January 13th.'?", "option_A": "Trump addressed the crowd.", "option_B": "A woman was shot inside the Capitol and died.", "option_C": "Congress confirmed Biden as president in the early hours of January 7th.", "option_D": "Trump supporters protested in Washington, D.C.", "golden_answer": "A,B,D"}
{"topic_id": 1, "uuid": "c97a374b-5843-41c0-bea8-9b972ba95e46", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'Sinn Fein called for a referendum on Irish unity.'?", "option_A": "Global markets plunged following the Brexit vote.", "option_B": "The United Kingdom held a referendum on June 23.", "option_C": "The nation divided into 'remain' and 'leave' camps.", "option_D": "David Cameron announced his resignation as Prime Minister.", "golden_answer": "A,B,C"}
{"topic_id": 4, "uuid": "64afc3de-56fc-4473-860b-c5e87bdc875d", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'Security arrested the suspected gunman, Tetsuya Yamagami.'?", "option_A": "Former Japanese Prime Minister Shinzo Abe was assassinated at a campaign rally.", "option_B": "The information provided is insufficient to determine the cause.", "option_C": "Shinzo Abe coined the phrase 'a free and open Indo-Pacific'.", "option_D": "A man fired twice at Shinzo Abe.", "golden_answer": "A,D"}
{"topic_id": 1, "uuid": "7ca8b264-7c60-46bb-a68b-e47fd0cca317", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'Over three million Brits called for a do-over.'?", "option_A": "The referendum date was set in February.", "option_B": "The information provided is insufficient to determine the cause.", "option_C": "David Cameron announced his resignation as Prime Minister.", "option_D": "Nicola Sturgeon stated the Scottish government would prepare legislation for a new independence referendum.", "golden_answer": "C"}
{"topic_id": 1, "uuid": "d69cf9c8-f55e-4cc9-b398-86b10b3bc004", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'Over three million Brits called for a do-over.'?", "option_A": "Global markets plunged following the Brexit vote.", "option_B": "Prime Minister David Cameron pledged a referendum on EU membership in 2013.", "option_C": "The referendum date was set in February.", "option_D": "The British pound plunged in value.", "golden_answer": "A,B"}
{"topic_id": 3, "uuid": "dca7853a-5212-4da0-8f09-bee0508ba9e3", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'Trump was permanently banned from Twitter on January 8th.'?", "option_A": "Trump urged supporters to march to the Capitol.", "option_B": "Pipe bombs were reported at the Republican National Committee building and the Democratic National Committee headquarters.", "option_C": "Protesters clashed with police and breached security barriers at the Capitol.", "option_D": "Trump supporters protested in Washington, D.C.", "golden_answer": "A,C,D"}
{"topic_id": 3, "uuid": "68b76634-d521-4e48-a4a5-1334eeb5c107", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'Twitter removed Trump's tweets and locked his account.'?", "option_A": "A woman was shot inside the Capitol and died.", "option_B": "Capitol Police Chief Steven Sund, House Sergeant at Arms Paul Irving, and Senate Sergeant at Arms Michael Stenger resigned.", "option_C": "The D.C. National Guard was activated, and a citywide curfew was imposed.", "option_D": "Trump addressed the crowd.", "golden_answer": "D"}
{"topic_id": 4, "uuid": "ad6ff05e-30d4-454b-92c2-13ee5702b812", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'Shinzo Abe was pronounced dead at 5:03 p.m.'?", "option_A": "The shooter used a handmade gun.", "option_B": "Former Japanese Prime Minister Shinzo Abe was assassinated at a campaign rally.", "option_C": "A man fired twice at Shinzo Abe.", "option_D": "Benjamin Netanyahu visited Tokyo in 2014.", "golden_answer": "A,B,C"}
{"topic_id": 3, "uuid": "0d5c8fe4-7235-4485-bd17-1b8ce3f3b13a", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'Trump was impeached for a second time on January 13th.'?", "option_A": "The Capitol was secured, and lawmakers reconvened to continue certification.", "option_B": "The information provided is insufficient to determine the cause.", "option_C": "The D.C. National Guard was activated, and a citywide curfew was imposed.", "option_D": "The House and Senate recessed, and the Capitol was locked down.", "golden_answer": "C,D"}
{"topic_id": 4, "uuid": "6f11397f-fcd0-4638-bebd-54f0dd6a0958", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'Videos of the assassination circulated on social media.'?", "option_A": "The information provided is insufficient to determine the cause.", "option_B": "A man fired twice at Shinzo Abe.", "option_C": "Shinzo Abe visited Jerusalem in 2018.", "option_D": "Shinzo Abe promoted the Quadrilateral Security Dialogue (Quad).", "golden_answer": "B"}
{"topic_id": 3, "uuid": "f3e99e21-c62a-441b-9076-8c6957a50ed6", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'The Capitol was secured, and lawmakers reconvened to continue certification.'?", "option_A": "The D.C. National Guard was activated, and a citywide curfew was imposed.", "option_B": "The congressional certification of Joe Biden’s victory was halted.", "option_C": "A woman was shot inside the Capitol and died.", "option_D": "Trump addressed the crowd.", "golden_answer": "A,B"}
{"topic_id": 3, "uuid": "6a6933ed-6030-4d30-9059-67a70425b309", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'Twitter removed Trump's tweets and locked his account.'?", "option_A": "The information provided is insufficient to determine the cause.", "option_B": "Capitol Police Chief Steven Sund, House Sergeant at Arms Paul Irving, and Senate Sergeant at Arms Michael Stenger resigned.", "option_C": "The House and Senate recessed, and the Capitol was locked down.", "option_D": "Trump addressed the crowd.", "golden_answer": "C,D"}
{"topic_id": 3, "uuid": "643703ce-89dd-4fa9-9e9c-aca38cc7c910", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'Protesters clashed with police and breached security barriers at the Capitol.'?", "option_A": "The information provided is insufficient to determine the cause.", "option_B": "Pipe bombs were reported at the Republican National Committee building and the Democratic National Committee headquarters.", "option_C": "Trump supporters protested in Washington, D.C.", "option_D": "Trump addressed the crowd.", "golden_answer": "C,D"}
{"topic_id": 1, "uuid": "9111d1d5-02d5-4215-87ac-2fcfe57225ab", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'The UK voted to leave the EU in a June 23 referendum.'?", "option_A": "The information provided is insufficient to determine the cause.", "option_B": "The Conservative Party won the election.", "option_C": "The United Kingdom held a referendum on June 23.", "option_D": "The referendum date was set in February.", "golden_answer": "B,C"}
{"topic_id": 1, "uuid": "609ec33f-3024-4406-9fe5-fe64daf79c58", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'Sinn Fein called for a referendum on Irish unity.'?", "option_A": "Nicola Sturgeon stated the Scottish government would prepare legislation for a new independence referendum.", "option_B": "The referendum date was set in February.", "option_C": "The nation divided into 'remain' and 'leave' camps.", "option_D": "Cameron's attempt to renegotiate the U.K.'s EU membership terms failed.", "golden_answer": "C"}
{"topic_id": 3, "uuid": "4e289b47-728a-41d4-bc43-3b69128aac79", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'Trump was permanently banned from Twitter on January 8th.'?", "option_A": "The FBI and ATF cleared the Capitol.", "option_B": "Five people died during the riots.", "option_C": "The Capitol was secured, and lawmakers reconvened to continue certification.", "option_D": "Congress confirmed Biden as president in the early hours of January 7th.", "golden_answer": "B"}
{"topic_id": 1, "uuid": "2e93d70b-fa38-4557-8273-f4a17814e647", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'The UK influenced EU initiatives, including the Europol Counter Terrorism Centre (CTC) and the PNRD.'?", "option_A": "Over three million Brits called for a do-over.", "option_B": "The UK voted to leave the EU in a June 23 referendum.", "option_C": "The United Kingdom held a referendum on June 23.", "option_D": "The UK drafted the EU Counter Terrorism Strategy in 2005.", "golden_answer": "D"}
{"topic_id": 4, "uuid": "954f9a9c-7c62-470f-82ac-93d0ece22fdc", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'Shinzo Abe promoted the Quadrilateral Security Dialogue (Quad).'?", "option_A": "Benjamin Netanyahu visited Tokyo in 2014.", "option_B": "The information provided is insufficient to determine the cause.", "option_C": "Shinzo Abe coined the phrase 'a free and open Indo-Pacific'.", "option_D": "Shinzo Abe became the deputy chief cabinet secretary in the early 2000s.", "golden_answer": "C"}
{"topic_id": 3, "uuid": "08526ce2-c523-4552-a210-fb26dea4c1a2", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'Protesters clashed with police and breached security barriers at the Capitol.'?", "option_A": "Trump addressed the crowd.", "option_B": "Trump supporters protested in Washington, D.C.", "option_C": "Trump urged supporters to march to the Capitol.", "option_D": "Pipe bombs were reported at the Republican National Committee building and the Democratic National Committee headquarters.", "golden_answer": "A,B,C"}
{"topic_id": 1, "uuid": "6d51c649-2e1e-4457-8714-8874f51d6069", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'David Cameron announced his resignation as Prime Minister.'?", "option_A": "Northern Ireland and Scotland voted to remain in the EU.", "option_B": "Prime Minister David Cameron pledged a referendum on EU membership in 2013.", "option_C": "The referendum date was set in February.", "option_D": "The United Kingdom held a referendum on June 23.", "golden_answer": "B,D"}
{"topic_id": 1, "uuid": "8a63ada1-b392-4aac-aaaa-d6e176782d75", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'David Cameron announced his resignation as Prime Minister.'?", "option_A": "Prime Minister David Cameron pledged a referendum on EU membership in 2013.", "option_B": "The United Kingdom held a referendum on June 23.", "option_C": "The UK voted to leave the EU in a June 23 referendum.", "option_D": "Northern Ireland and Scotland voted to remain in the EU.", "golden_answer": "A,B,C"}
{"topic_id": 3, "uuid": "0080fe55-cbf6-4359-aeb8-ab7bbe82974d", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'The Capitol was secured, and lawmakers reconvened to continue certification.'?", "option_A": "Trump urged supporters to march to the Capitol.", "option_B": "Supporters stormed the U.S. Capitol.", "option_C": "Protesters clashed with police and breached security barriers at the Capitol.", "option_D": "The House and Senate recessed, and the Capitol was locked down.", "golden_answer": "B,C,D"}
{"topic_id": 4, "uuid": "bd1505af-9a91-43a0-ac9e-855029cdd9c1", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'Social media companies removed harmful content.'?", "option_A": "Videos of the assassination circulated on social media.", "option_B": "Former Japanese Prime Minister Shinzo Abe was assassinated at a campaign rally.", "option_C": "A man fired twice at Shinzo Abe.", "option_D": "Shinzo Abe returned to office in 2012 and later became the longest-serving prime minister.", "golden_answer": "A,B,C"}
{"topic_id": 1, "uuid": "b7a242ba-3ff3-49df-a673-b5cf5a0b63f0", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'The British pound plunged in value.'?", "option_A": "The United Kingdom held a referendum on June 23.", "option_B": "Northern Ireland and Scotland voted to remain in the EU.", "option_C": "Prime Minister David Cameron pledged a referendum on EU membership in 2013.", "option_D": "The UK voted to leave the EU in a June 23 referendum.", "golden_answer": "A,C,D"}
{"topic_id": 3, "uuid": "855b55b2-7829-4f28-92e6-2af5a5426138", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'Capitol Police Chief Steven Sund, House Sergeant at Arms Paul Irving, and Senate Sergeant at Arms Michael Stenger resigned.'?", "option_A": "Pipe bombs were reported at the Republican National Committee building and the Democratic National Committee headquarters.", "option_B": "Congress confirmed Biden as president in the early hours of January 7th.", "option_C": "The House and Senate recessed, and the Capitol was locked down.", "option_D": "The FBI and ATF cleared the Capitol.", "golden_answer": "B,C"}
{"topic_id": 1, "uuid": "1992a013-6ca7-476f-a46d-2a5e2c5e1bab", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'Over three million Brits called for a do-over.'?", "option_A": "Prime Minister David Cameron pledged a referendum on EU membership in 2013.", "option_B": "David Cameron announced his resignation as Prime Minister.", "option_C": "Global markets plunged following the Brexit vote.", "option_D": "The referendum date was set in February.", "golden_answer": "A,B,C"}
{"topic_id": 4, "uuid": "e52ac663-a7d6-4057-94ac-effc21e6dcb7", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'Security arrested the suspected gunman, Tetsuya Yamagami.'?", "option_A": "Shinzo Abe reinterpreted Japan's constitution in 2014.", "option_B": "A man fired twice at Shinzo Abe.", "option_C": "Shinzo Abe coined the phrase 'a free and open Indo-Pacific'.", "option_D": "Shinzo Abe promoted the Quadrilateral Security Dialogue (Quad).", "golden_answer": "B"}
{"topic_id": 4, "uuid": "edfb0975-ad4f-4663-af98-bf83e7ea91b7", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'Videos of the assassination circulated on social media.'?", "option_A": "A man fired twice at Shinzo Abe.", "option_B": "Shinzo Abe visited Jerusalem in 2018.", "option_C": "Former Japanese Prime Minister Shinzo Abe was assassinated at a campaign rally.", "option_D": "Shinzo Abe became the youngest prime minister in postwar Japan in 2006.", "golden_answer": "A,C"}
{"topic_id": 1, "uuid": "cfb4d18b-3f9b-4538-a16e-12562ccca0cb", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'Global markets plunged following the Brexit vote.'?", "option_A": "The referendum date was set in February.", "option_B": "The information provided is insufficient to determine the cause.", "option_C": "The UK voted to leave the EU in a June 23 referendum.", "option_D": "David Cameron announced his resignation as Prime Minister.", "golden_answer": "C"}
{"topic_id": 1, "uuid": "ea586d43-4c1d-49c5-b8a4-d4da317b1f90", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'The United Kingdom held a referendum on June 23.'?", "option_A": "The referendum date was set in February.", "option_B": "The information provided is insufficient to determine the cause.", "option_C": "Prime Minister David Cameron pledged a referendum on EU membership in 2013.", "option_D": "The nation divided into 'remain' and 'leave' camps.", "golden_answer": "A,C"}
{"topic_id": 4, "uuid": "7952942c-ad16-45e2-bb21-4b834e13f039", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'Shinzo Abe was pronounced dead at 5:03 p.m.'?", "option_A": "Shinzo Abe visited Jerusalem in 2018.", "option_B": "Shinzo Abe returned to office in 2012 and later became the longest-serving prime minister.", "option_C": "A man fired twice at Shinzo Abe.", "option_D": "Yoshihide Suga succeeded Shinzo Abe in September 2020.", "golden_answer": "C"}
{"topic_id": 3, "uuid": "48542c4f-d370-424f-9e17-f2dc45c02cac", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'The D.C. National Guard was activated, and a citywide curfew was imposed.'?", "option_A": "Trump supporters protested in Washington, D.C.", "option_B": "The information provided is insufficient to determine the cause.", "option_C": "The House and Senate recessed, and the Capitol was locked down.", "option_D": "Trump urged supporters to march to the Capitol.", "golden_answer": "A,C,D"}
{"topic_id": 4, "uuid": "c226a4e5-6e18-4afc-b6ba-74a1b47cac9c", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'Shinzo Abe was pronounced dead at 5:03 p.m.'?", "option_A": "Benjamin Netanyahu visited Tokyo in 2014.", "option_B": "A man fired twice at Shinzo Abe.", "option_C": "Shinzo Abe became the youngest prime minister in postwar Japan in 2006.", "option_D": "The shooter used a handmade gun.", "golden_answer": "B,D"}
{"topic_id": 4, "uuid": "15c7d9d2-d7fc-45e4-b415-9ee88b7c4690", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'Security arrested the suspected gunman, Tetsuya Yamagami.'?", "option_A": "Former Japanese Prime Minister Shinzo Abe was assassinated at a campaign rally.", "option_B": "Shinzo Abe became the youngest prime minister in postwar Japan in 2006.", "option_C": "Shinzo Abe became the deputy chief cabinet secretary in the early 2000s.", "option_D": "The information provided is insufficient to determine the cause.", "golden_answer": "A"}
{"topic_id": 3, "uuid": "e7816c1b-995d-4451-9441-6543fedd0fd0", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'Supporters stormed the U.S. Capitol.'?", "option_A": "Trump urged supporters to march to the Capitol.", "option_B": "Protesters clashed with police and breached security barriers at the Capitol.", "option_C": "The information provided is insufficient to determine the cause.", "option_D": "Trump addressed the crowd.", "golden_answer": "A,B,D"}
{"topic_id": 3, "uuid": "32fe2e0a-e30a-4e38-a31a-ba791da82004", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'The congressional certification of Joe Biden’s victory was halted.'?", "option_A": "Trump supporters protested in Washington, D.C.", "option_B": "Protesters clashed with police and breached security barriers at the Capitol.", "option_C": "Pipe bombs were reported at the Republican National Committee building and the Democratic National Committee headquarters.", "option_D": "The information provided is insufficient to determine the cause.", "golden_answer": "A,B"}
{"topic_id": 3, "uuid": "4b31b599-3909-4645-8038-b41f8aa56113", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'Congress confirmed Biden as president in the early hours of January 7th.'?", "option_A": "The D.C. National Guard was activated, and a citywide curfew was imposed.", "option_B": "Protesters clashed with police and breached security barriers at the Capitol.", "option_C": "The congressional certification of Joe Biden’s victory was halted.", "option_D": "Trump urged supporters to march to the Capitol.", "golden_answer": "C"}
{"topic_id": 3, "uuid": "9aae6698-b03a-4731-87b1-886c5418bf50", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'The Capitol was secured, and lawmakers reconvened to continue certification.'?", "option_A": "Pipe bombs were reported at the Republican National Committee building and the Democratic National Committee headquarters.", "option_B": "The House and Senate recessed, and the Capitol was locked down.", "option_C": "The information provided is insufficient to determine the cause.", "option_D": "A woman was shot inside the Capitol and died.", "golden_answer": "B"}
{"topic_id": 3, "uuid": "c01c3edc-98aa-4ef4-b420-a42388f6f71a", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'Congress confirmed Biden as president in the early hours of January 7th.'?", "option_A": "The FBI and ATF cleared the Capitol.", "option_B": "The Capitol was secured, and lawmakers reconvened to continue certification.", "option_C": "Five people died during the riots.", "option_D": "Trump supporters protested in Washington, D.C.", "golden_answer": "A,B"}
{"topic_id": 1, "uuid": "21f4ae9e-bfb3-42d3-872d-2cfabb2ccef7", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'Global markets plunged following the Brexit vote.'?", "option_A": "David Cameron announced his resignation as Prime Minister.", "option_B": "The United Kingdom held a referendum on June 23.", "option_C": "The UK voted to leave the EU in a June 23 referendum.", "option_D": "The Conservative Party won the election.", "golden_answer": "B,C,D"}
{"topic_id": 4, "uuid": "e488e6dd-56ad-448c-a691-c0b3826ed323", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'World leaders expressed shock and condemned the murder.'?", "option_A": "A man fired twice at Shinzo Abe.", "option_B": "Benjamin Netanyahu visited Tokyo in 2014.", "option_C": "The information provided is insufficient to determine the cause.", "option_D": "Shinzo Abe returned to office in 2012 and later became the longest-serving prime minister.", "golden_answer": "A"}
{"topic_id": 1, "uuid": "c70c2385-74f8-4e8d-83da-7441a21feb0d", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'The United Kingdom held a referendum on June 23.'?", "option_A": "The referendum date was set in February.", "option_B": "The nation divided into 'remain' and 'leave' camps.", "option_C": "The Conservative Party won the election.", "option_D": "Prime Minister David Cameron pledged a referendum on EU membership in 2013.", "golden_answer": "A,C,D"}
{"topic_id": 3, "uuid": "9f32856e-75ad-4369-8d8b-ff80ae5163a7", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'The FBI and ATF cleared the Capitol.'?", "option_A": "The information provided is insufficient to determine the cause.", "option_B": "Pipe bombs were reported at the Republican National Committee building and the Democratic National Committee headquarters.", "option_C": "Supporters stormed the U.S. Capitol.", "option_D": "Five people died during the riots.", "golden_answer": "C"}
{"topic_id": 3, "uuid": "f8c6c2d9-da2b-49cc-8c5c-e431034ed69a", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'Five people died during the riots.'?", "option_A": "Trump urged supporters to march to the Capitol.", "option_B": "The information provided is insufficient to determine the cause.", "option_C": "The House and Senate recessed, and the Capitol was locked down.", "option_D": "Supporters stormed the U.S. Capitol.", "golden_answer": "A,C,D"}
{"topic_id": 4, "uuid": "81507bc1-af7f-434e-8994-2cbb8775583a", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'World leaders expressed shock and condemned the murder.'?", "option_A": "A man fired twice at Shinzo Abe.", "option_B": "Shinzo Abe was pronounced dead at 5:03 p.m.", "option_C": "Shinzo Abe visited Jerusalem in 2018.", "option_D": "Former Japanese Prime Minister Shinzo Abe was assassinated at a campaign rally.", "golden_answer": "A,B,D"}
{"topic_id": 3, "uuid": "31f07cb9-e789-4a82-8450-b9e1b1a0b24e", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'The House and Senate recessed, and the Capitol was locked down.'?", "option_A": "The information provided is insufficient to determine the cause.", "option_B": "Pipe bombs were reported at the Republican National Committee building and the Democratic National Committee headquarters.", "option_C": "Trump addressed the crowd.", "option_D": "Supporters stormed the U.S. Capitol.", "golden_answer": "C,D"}
{"topic_id": 4, "uuid": "613823ef-84d1-4b44-8388-d0be74c30e31", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'Social media companies removed harmful content.'?", "option_A": "Shinzo Abe returned to office in 2012 and later became the longest-serving prime minister.", "option_B": "A man fired twice at Shinzo Abe.", "option_C": "Explosives were found at Tetsuya Yamagami's home.", "option_D": "The shooter used a handmade gun.", "golden_answer": "B"}
{"topic_id": 4, "uuid": "6dcd28e0-6420-42a9-b3d1-f5a747cc6f9e", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'World leaders expressed shock and condemned the murder.'?", "option_A": "A man fired twice at Shinzo Abe.", "option_B": "Security arrested the suspected gunman, Tetsuya Yamagami.", "option_C": "Former Japanese Prime Minister Shinzo Abe was assassinated at a campaign rally.", "option_D": "Shinzo Abe became the youngest prime minister in postwar Japan in 2006.", "golden_answer": "A,C"}
{"topic_id": 1, "uuid": "e7bfb89d-4774-476a-bba1-5dac930f7ce6", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'David Cameron announced his resignation as Prime Minister.'?", "option_A": "Northern Ireland and Scotland voted to remain in the EU.", "option_B": "The Conservative Party won the election.", "option_C": "The information provided is insufficient to determine the cause.", "option_D": "Prime Minister David Cameron pledged a referendum on EU membership in 2013.", "golden_answer": "D"}
{"topic_id": 3, "uuid": "56c4bb87-20cb-4bf5-890d-515fdaba35e7", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'Trump was permanently banned from Twitter on January 8th.'?", "option_A": "Congress confirmed Biden as president in the early hours of January 7th.", "option_B": "Five people died during the riots.", "option_C": "Pipe bombs were reported at the Republican National Committee building and the Democratic National Committee headquarters.", "option_D": "Supporters stormed the U.S. Capitol.", "golden_answer": "B,D"}
{"topic_id": 1, "uuid": "6fb656c1-0d22-4fcb-b046-64252ed4a586", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'Global markets plunged following the Brexit vote.'?", "option_A": "David Cameron announced his resignation as Prime Minister.", "option_B": "The United Kingdom held a referendum on June 23.", "option_C": "The referendum date was set in February.", "option_D": "The UK voted to leave the EU in a June 23 referendum.", "golden_answer": "B,D"}
{"topic_id": 4, "uuid": "ad96be5e-c6f2-4757-8095-a123bb34e06a", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'Social media companies removed harmful content.'?", "option_A": "Explosives were found at Tetsuya Yamagami's home.", "option_B": "Videos of the assassination circulated on social media.", "option_C": "Shinzo Abe returned to office in 2012 and later became the longest-serving prime minister.", "option_D": "Former Japanese Prime Minister Shinzo Abe was assassinated at a campaign rally.", "golden_answer": "B,D"}
{"topic_id": 1, "uuid": "dd2a4ba5-cdf9-48b7-b154-ce1523a5e37b", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'Nicola Sturgeon stated the Scottish government would prepare legislation for a new independence referendum.'?", "option_A": "The nation divided into 'remain' and 'leave' camps.", "option_B": "The information provided is insufficient to determine the cause.", "option_C": "The Conservative Party won the election.", "option_D": "David Cameron announced his resignation as Prime Minister.", "golden_answer": "A"}
{"topic_id": 1, "uuid": "ba7b95ce-706c-484f-bced-1e4ff45d2d43", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'Sinn Fein called for a referendum on Irish unity.'?", "option_A": "The nation divided into 'remain' and 'leave' camps.", "option_B": "Global markets plunged following the Brexit vote.", "option_C": "Cameron's attempt to renegotiate the U.K.'s EU membership terms failed.", "option_D": "Nicola Sturgeon stated the Scottish government would prepare legislation for a new independence referendum.", "golden_answer": "A,B"}
{"topic_id": 3, "uuid": "3a2d5edd-b9d1-4c90-acd1-e4046fc29eba", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'The House and Senate recessed, and the Capitol was locked down.'?", "option_A": "Trump addressed the crowd.", "option_B": "Supporters stormed the U.S. Capitol.", "option_C": "Trump supporters protested in Washington, D.C.", "option_D": "The information provided is insufficient to determine the cause.", "golden_answer": "A,B,C"}
{"topic_id": 3, "uuid": "202d4f53-41e7-470a-bf2e-03a68978bd01", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'Five people died during the riots.'?", "option_A": "Supporters stormed the U.S. Capitol.", "option_B": "Pipe bombs were reported at the Republican National Committee building and the Democratic National Committee headquarters.", "option_C": "Trump supporters protested in Washington, D.C.", "option_D": "The information provided is insufficient to determine the cause.", "golden_answer": "A,C"}
{"topic_id": 3, "uuid": "b8ee91d8-2b62-4aa5-ba3d-b5617a28b4a4", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'The congressional certification of Joe Biden’s victory was halted.'?", "option_A": "The House and Senate recessed, and the Capitol was locked down.", "option_B": "A woman was shot inside the Capitol and died.", "option_C": "Supporters stormed the U.S. Capitol.", "option_D": "Trump urged supporters to march to the Capitol.", "golden_answer": "A,C,D"}
{"topic_id": 1, "uuid": "4706fa62-aae1-4c6a-bff7-f34dcdb111cc", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'The UK voted to leave the EU in a June 23 referendum.'?", "option_A": "The Conservative Party won the election.", "option_B": "The referendum date was set in February.", "option_C": "Prime Minister David Cameron pledged a referendum on EU membership in 2013.", "option_D": "The United Kingdom held a referendum on June 23.", "golden_answer": "A,C,D"}
{"topic_id": 1, "uuid": "32d250d2-a0cc-49d7-a811-b38266f7953e", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'Nicola Sturgeon stated the Scottish government would prepare legislation for a new independence referendum.'?", "option_A": "David Cameron announced his resignation as Prime Minister.", "option_B": "The nation divided into 'remain' and 'leave' camps.", "option_C": "Prime Minister David Cameron pledged a referendum on EU membership in 2013.", "option_D": "The information provided is insufficient to determine the cause.", "golden_answer": "B,C"}
